Taylor Bleizeffer

307-267-9404 www.taylorbleizeffer.com taylorbleizeffer@gmail.com 3544 Gilpin St, Denver CO, 80205

Profile

I am a curious person and a deep, analytical thinker. This allows me to fully understand problems and see them from many different angles to arrive at proper solutions. I value creativity and enjoy hobbies such as playing the guitar and bass, and photography. In the workplace, I strive to create an environment that is both productive and enjoyable by keeping a positive attitude. I recently graduated from the University of Wyoming with a Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science (December, 2020).

Skills

The strengths I bring to any position include excellent communication, great problem-solving, knowledge, and comfort with technology. Analytical thinking allows me to assess situations accurately, create efficient plans of action, and find the tools I need to get the job done. The work I have done in my Computer Science degree has prepared me for many different aspects of the field. I am comfortable in the C++, Java, HTML, CSS and JavaScript programming languages. Android development in Java and Kotlin, Haskell, SQLite and C# are a few more languages I've had experience with through my studies. I gained much experience with version control using Git during my studies. I have also been introduced to basic networking including basic router/switch configuration and troubleshooting. Other skills include familiarity with the image editing software like Gimp, making basic 2D video games in GameMaker Studio and some experience composing, recording and mixing with DAWs.

Education

University of Wyoming – Laramie, WY Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science (2020), 3.0 GPA

Casper College – Casper, WY Associate of Engineering in Computer Science (2017), 3.0 GPA

Kelly Walsh High School – Casper, WY (Graduated 2014), 3.0 GPA

Relevant Coursework Complete

Intro to Computer Science Intro to Digital Electronics Computer Science 1 & 2 Computer Organization JavaScript Programming Java Programming

Coursework continued...

Inter-networking 1 & 2
Algorithms & Data Structures
Functional Programming
Software Design
Operating System Design
Computer Security
Mobile Programming 1
Adv. Mobile Programming
Artificial Intelligence
Web Application Development
Philosophy of Science

Experience

Student researcher, Rochester Institute of Technology – "Cultivating Next Generation Software Engineers" REU; Rochester, NY – May 2019 – August 2019:

Student researcher, served on research team working closely with mentor professor and team members to plan, design and perform research; developed web scraper using Ruby to collect data for research; gave weekly status updates presenting our progress, setbacks, and plan for the next week to mentor professors and other research teams.

Delivery driver, Jimmy John's; Laramie, WY – July 2017 – July 2020:

Customer service; food preparation; fulfill delivery orders safely; accurately and quickly; safe food handling; work in team-oriented environment; answer and troubleshoot customer questions and complaints.

Delivery driver, Jimmy John's; Casper, WY – Sep 2016 – July 2017

Bassist, Fathom All the Animals; Denver, CO – Spring 2015 – Present:

Teamwork; creativity; social and performance skills; marketing/advertising; managing band social media presence; order and sell merchandise; money and time management; musical composition and practice; travel; networking with other musicians, promoters, venues, etc.

Line server, Qdoba Mexican Grill; Casper, WY – Sep 2012 – Aug 2014, Dec 2015 – June 2016: Customer service; food preparation; fulfill customer orders accurately; work in team-oriented environment; answer and troubleshoot customer questions/complaints; maintain knowledge of menu to provide customers with accurate information and make suggestions for flavor pairings; keeping restaurant clean and presentable; paying attention to details.

Delivery driver, Domino's Pizza; Casper, WY – Jan 2015 – Feb 2015, Loveland CO – June 2016 – Sep 2016:

Customer service; fulfill delivery orders safely; accurately and quickly; safe food handling; work in team-oriented environment; answer or troubleshoot customer questions and complaints.

Front Desk Clerk, C'mon Inn Hotel & Suites; Evansville, WY – June 2015 – Dec 2015: Customer service; maintain meticulous records of current guests (room numbers, vehicle and credit card information); perform daily audit to maintain accurate guest and accounting records; make sure lobby, hallways, conference rooms, etc. are clean and presentable; prepare conference rooms; answer or troubleshoot guest questions and complaints; answer phones and make reservations; provide guests with information about local businesses and events; create a welcoming and homely environment for guests.

Video Technician, University of Wyoming Outreach School; Laramie, WY – Sep 2014 – June 2015: Properly handle and operate classroom technology; maintain connection with off-site classrooms; troubleshoot issues with devices and software (cameras, mics, computers, streaming program); communicate with instructors and students to facilitate on-line lectures; display PowerPoints, videos, camera angles, monitors etc. as needed by instructor and students; maintain a report of every lecture (attendance, issues, events of note, general summary).

Programs

Cultivating Next Generation Software Engineering Researchers REU Program – Rochester Institute of Technology – Rochester, NY 2019

School of Energy Resources Summer Camp – University of Wyoming – Laramie, WY 2012 and 2013

Awakening Summer Internship – Antioch Church – Overland Park, KS 2011 and 2012

References

Professional:

Yi Wang – REU Mentor – Rochester, NY - oliver.wangyi@gmail.com Mehdi Mirakhorli – REU Mentor – Rochester, NY - mxmvse@rit.edu David Johnson – Fellow musician – Casper, WY – 307-797-7452 Thomas Wilkinson – Coworker/Classmate – Laramie, WY – 720-273-3154

Personal:

John Scozzafava – Uncle – Laramie, WY – 307-399-5804